RYAN SARIEGO

<u>LINKEDIN.COM/IN/RSARIEGO</u> • <u>NO-PICKLES.COM</u> • <u>GITHUB.COM/NOPICKLESPLEASE</u>

NEW YORK, NY • (917) 750-6545 • <u>RSARIEGO@FASTMAIL.COM</u>

SUMMARY & TECHNICAL PROFICIENCIES

Developed web applications as a personal interest for 20+ years and recently completed a full-stack development bootcamp to obtain the additional skills necessary to finally make it a professional career.

Technical Proficiencies • JavaScript, Node.js, React.js, Redux.js, React Router, Express, PostgreSQL, RESTful API, Git, HTML, CSS, Tailwind, Material-UI, Responsive Design

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

Serenade • Al-Curated Spotify Playlist Generator (Link) • Lead Front-End Developer

JUL. 2023

- Integrated OpenAI's DaVinci model & Spotify API to interpret user prompts for creative playlist generation
- Responsible for UX design, Profile & My Playlists components, JSX rendering of playlists, responsive design

Just a Calculator • Camouflaged Bitcoin Portfolio Tracker (Link) • Creator, Developer

JUN. 2023

- Financial portfolio app with CoinMarketCap API implementation for providing extensive real-time statistics
- · Responsible for full-stack app infrastructure, Postgres database, UX design, responsive design for mobile

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Precision Surgical Inc. • NYC • Account Executive, CRM Ops. Manager

2012 - PRESENT

- Surgical sales rep. solely responsible for \$2+ million annual quota, 50+ healthcare facility clients
- Manage entire sales cycle, from consultation to equipment planning, implementation & clinical training
- · Assisted development of a customized CRM web platform for client tracking, sales docs, data analytics

Native English Language Institute • Santiago, Chile • ESL Instructor

2011 - 2012

· Designed custom course curriculum & materials by occupational field, exams for career advancement

EDUCATION & ADDITIONAL SKILLS

Fullstack Academy • Remote • Web Development Bootcamp

DEC. 2022 - JUN. 2023

U. of Michigan • Remote • Getting Started with Python (Certificate Program)

AUG. 2021

New England Institute of Art • Boston • B.S., Audio Engineering

2003 - 2006

Additional Skills • Music & Podcast Production (Logic Pro), Graphic Design, Photo Editing, Conversant Spanish